GABRIEL DRAY

dray.gabriel@yahoo.com 22yo (+33) 06.52.61.73.32

PROFILE

Graduated with a Big Data Bachelor and finishing a degree Master in IT Finance at Paris Dauphine. Have 1 year of internship experience building and testing data model as Data Scientist in Allianz France. Decisive in the strategic and financial choices of IT projects. Last year, negotiate customer contract at €10k thanks to Benchmarking, improvement of 45% customer experience performance

LINKS

Portfolio : gabrieldray.netlify.app

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/gabriel-dray-42a5631a0

• SKILLS •

Computer Programming: Python, Java, VBA, Web (Js, Html, Css), Flutter

Microsoft Office Package : VBA, Excel, Access, Power BI, Word, Powerpoint

GIT

Database / Visualization : SQL, (mongoDB, FireBase, MySQL..), FileMaker Pro Advanced, QLike, Sheets

LANGUAGES

FRENCH: Native ENGLISH: Advanced Low SPANISH: Novice High HEBREW: Novice

HOBBIES

Traveling, Cinema and Comedy, Sports (Football, Handball, Basketball, Golf) American/Japanese Culture

EDUCATION

Dauphine PSL, Paris

<u>Master of IT, Decision, Data</u> - September 2021 – August 2023 IA / Data fundamentals: Game Theory, Machine Learning, Programming, Graph Theory, Maths

ESGI, Paris

<u>Bachelor in Big Data & Artificial Intelligence</u> - September 2020 - August 2021 Python - Java Development for Data Environment, Machine Learning, Maths, SQL

University of Paris Descartes, Paris

<u>Associate's Degree in Computer Science</u> - September 2018 – August 2020 Computer Science : Maths, Object-Oriented-Programming, Web programming, Database

Alliance High School, Paris

<u>High School Diploma with Honors in Science</u> - September 2015 – June 2018

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

UB Partner, Paris

BI Developer - September 2021 - August 2022

- Automation of accounting files with Excel
- Data visualization preparation
- Bench-marking of financial listed companies
- Queries in SQL, Scrapping/Parsing in python

Allianz, Paris La Défense

<u>Data Scientist Intern</u> - September 2020 - August 2021

- Insurance Data management
- Automation of ML applications
- Data Analysis / Visualization : Creation of KPI Dashboard

SELARL AWADA Surgical practice, Paris

<u>Full Stack Developer Intern</u> - March 2020 - August 2020

COURSES

<u>Ethereum & Solidity: Complete Developer's Guide, Udemy</u> July 2022

Python For Financial Analysis And Algorithmic Trading, Udemy

February 2021 – March 2021